question_data = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The word &quot;news&quot; originates from the first letters of "
                     "the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
}
